<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CribbageGame</string>
    <string name="discard">     One player is assigned dealer at the beginning of each round and switches off every round. Dealer deals 6 cards to each player.
        Dealer then cuts deck, and non-dealer flips over top card (this is done for you in our game).
        One point goes to the non-dealer if the card flipped over is a Jack.
        Each player discards two cards from their hand to the \'crib\'. That crib now belongs to the dealer for later. </string>
    <string name="duel">        Non-dealer lays a card on the table faced up, followed by dealer and alternating until both have emptied their hands.
        Ranks of cards are summed as they are placed on the table. Points are gained by the owner of last card played if\:
            1\) Total = 15 \(\+2 pts\),
            2\) Previous card\(s\) have same rank as placed card (+2 pts per pair),
            3\) Any permutation of 3 or more straight cards forms a run (+n pts)
        The total of that sum is always capped at 31. If player has no cards that keep the sum below or at 31, the player should say \"Go\".
        Opponent then must play cards until no valid moves are available. Opponent to the player who said \"Go\" gains 2 pts for if the total reaches exactly 31, and 1 pt otherwise.
        After the opponent is appropriately awarded \"Go\" points, the round score resets, and play continues with next player\'s card until no cards remain.
        The cards available for scoring during this phase usually reset with the round score, but to simplify, this is not true for this project. </string>
    <string name="count">        The round ends when both players have no cards in their hands, the crib is full, and presumably the table is full of cards.
        Each player recollects their cards into their hand, and dealer claims the crib.
        Non-dealer tallies up points within hand and flipped card\:
            \+2 pts for any combination of cards totaling 15
            \+2 pts for any pair \(thus +6 pts for triple and +12 pts for quadruple\)
            \+n pts for a run of n \(must be 3 or more\)
            \+1 pt if hand contains jack of the same suit as flipped card
        Process repeats with dealer\'s hand, then with \"crib\" \(points go to dealer\)</string>
</resources>